<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Garden and Parks -->
    <string name="category_park">Parks</string>

    <string name="malampuzha">Malampuzha Gardens</string>
    <string name="malampuzha_description">Malampuzha Garden is a beautifully landscaped garden on
        the front side of the Malampuzha Dam. It is full of lush green lawns with well laid-out
        flower beds.</string>

    <string name="fantasy">Fantasy Park</string>
    <string name="fantasy_description">Fantasy Park is the first amusement park in Kerala. The
        attractions include 16D Cine Magic Ride, Planetarium, Dragon Coaster, Super Splash...</string>

    <!-- Waterfalls -->
    <string name="category_waterfalls">Waterfalls</string>

    <string name="dhoni">Dhoni Waterfalls</string>
    <string name="dhoni_description">Dhoni hills in Palakkad is popular picnic spot with a small and
        beautiful waterfall. It takes a three hours trek from the base of the Dhoni hills to reach
        this reserve forest area.</string>

    <string name="meenvallam">Meenvallam</string>
    <string name="meenvallam_description">Meenvallam Waterfalls is situated in Palakkad district.
        Originating from the Thuppanadu River - a part of Western Ghats, these falls drop step by
        step from a height of 5 to 45 metres.</string>

    <!-- Landmarks -->
    <string name="category_landmarks">Landmarks</string>

    <string name="palakkad_fort">Palakkad Fort</string>
    <string name="palakkad_fort_description">Palakkad Fort also known as Tipu sultan\'s Fort is an old fort
        situated in the heart of Palakkad town of Kerala state, southern India.
        It was built by Haider Ali in 1766 ACE and remains one of the best preserved forts in Kerala.</string>

    <string name="seethagrundu">Seethagrundu</string>
    <string name="seethagrundu_description">Seetharkundu Viewpoint is situated at a distance of 8Kms
        from Nelliyampathy. One of the prime attractions here is the waterfall. A stream runs down
        from here to form a small lake.</string>

    <!-- Nature -->
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>

    <string name="nelliyampathi">Nelliyampathi</string>
    <string name="nelliyampathi_description">Nelliyampathy (also spelled Nelliampathi) is a hill
        station 60 kilometres (37 mi) from Palakkad, state of Kerala, India. Nelliampathy is
        surrounded by tea and coffee plantations. </string>

    <string name="parambikulam">Parambikulam</string>
    <string name="parambikulam_description">A jungle safari which will quench one’s desire to
        witness all important wildlife in the park. A 3 ½ hour jungle safari will reveal the inner
        secrets of Parambikulam to outside world.</string>

</resources>
